Uh hello everyone. Today I'm going to
like them present and demonstrate about
my music player app that I have made
using Python And this is my code. I have
imported like firstly I have imported the
necessary modules like TK, enter, pie,
game, time, mutagen, threading, pile,
image and random and these are the
the path of for the files that I'll be
using. Which are the name list for the
accounts, the database for the music and
I mean and playlist is. The playlist for
individual users and here are the files.
So this name file consists of the.
The e-mail address,  thepassword and this
is a user ID that I've given to each new
new user and playlist is for each.
This is the user ID and this is their
playlist for each users in the song DB in
some database. Here are all the songs
that I currently have. And yeah this
sound did we just stores all the song
name of the songs that I currently have
in my database. No. Yeah in this in this
is like initializing some of the
variables.
Now this is so the playlist will be
empty. Since you're using a sketch, your
playlist won't be saved and you won't
have a playlist. And you can open your
playlist here using this button. Here
this is like the volume control and all
this is the shuffle button and this is
the loop button. This is backward.
Forward, Start, Pause and end button. You
click this button to close out of the
program. And now let's
But if you log in as a guest and next
time, your playlist still won't be there.
And that's like the one of the bad things
about log using my music player as a
guest. Now for the register and login
functions. So you will need to register an
e-mail first. Uh, the e-mail format has
to be correct. Or else it will if you
click register typing anything, OK, it
was pop up an error. To show that you'd
have to type in a valid e-mail format@
whichisexamplemail. com or something
else. So uh, even if you only type like
1.1 some, uh add something, it still
won't work. You need to have the full
e-mail format.
I'll just type in the random e-mail 6 and
this button is show to show the password
that we've typing like more for more
privacy. What is your? I'll just type it.
Yeah, register. OK, successfully register
and now it will bring us back to that
music player and we can log in using
the e-mail that  you'veregistered. I see
it's a bad. As it is.
OK.
Name.
156 7456. com.
And now we're in the music players and we
can add songs. As as in as, like with the
guest you can just add some any songs
that you like and you can play them.
Like so for the loop function. I'll show
you that it works using the loop
function. So basically when the song
finishes playing they will auto repeat
the song again.
it for my music player and to show some
error handling. We're logging, We're
logging in. So when you're registering an
e-mail. We've already
registered that e-mail, so if we register
this e-mail again, it will show that. An
account has already been registered using
the same e-mail and if we type in the
password. So you've received an e-mail
and we type in the password that is
lesser than 8 characters, it'll it'll
it'll pop up a message saying invalid
password. And if we try logging in.
156. com.
And if you type in the wrong password, it
would just pop up incorrect password.
It'll deny our access to the music,
video, music player.
And if you're playing and no matter if we
pause, like. Re pause the song, the
animation will also stop along with the
songs we need to continue. It will just
keep on moving. We stop the sound
completely. This will return to 0 and the
animation will. OK, yeah, that's it for
the music player.